http://www.nissan.com.au/privacy.html

Nissan Motor Co. (Australia) Privacy Policy
This is the Privacy Policy of Nissan Motor Co. (Australia) Pty Ltd ABN 54 004 663 156. We may change this policy by publishing an updated version on this website.
1. What personal information about you do we collect and hold?
We may collect and hold personal information about you. This includes:
your name, address, email, telephone number, date of birth and other information about you such as age and gender;
details about your vehicle purchase and servicing such as purchase date, purchase details, vehicle registration, name of selling dealer, service history and repair, warranty and recall details;
information you give us, such as when you contact our Customer Service Centre, login to our website, or call our roadside assistance;
from marketing campaigns, product surveys, and research, when you access and use our social media platforms and any publicly available information;
any other personal information we have to collect to identify you;
details in identity documents given to us, such as passport number, driver’s licence number, Medicare card number; and
payment details including bank account, credit card details and other payment information if you buy our products and services.
We will only collect sensitive information about you if you agree, unless the law lets us, or when the law says that we must collect it. Sensitive information includes information about your religious beliefs, ethnic origin, race and health.
If you give us personal information about another person, please tell them you have given it and tell them about this policy.
We keep records of privacy consents that we get from you.
We hold your personal information in secure electronic and physical files.
2. How do we collect and hold your personal information?
Usually we collect personal information about you from you and from Nissan dealers who received information from you.
We may collect personal information about you:
when you contact us by email, phone, in person, by SMS or other forms of communication, including our website or our social media platforms;
when you take part in promotions, competitions, customer surveys, and sponsorships;
when you fill in order forms for a vehicle, parts or accessories, or book your vehicle for servicing;
when you contact us about any of our products and services; or
from related companies, dealers and our service providers (such as Roadside Assist).
We may also collect personal information about you from other people such as:
your insurer or broker;
our agents;
any government authorities;
marketing agencies and marketing lists; and
other people you refer to us or who refer us to you.
3. What do we do with your personal information?
We collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for:
meeting our obligations to you (including warranty, recall, and roadside assistance) as the owner or driver of a vehicle;
answering your inquiries or comments;
customer service and product development;
to assess your application for a product or service;
developing, administering and managing our services and businesses;
promotions and marketing including direct marketing;
research to improve our websites, products or services;
any other customer support purposes;
dealing with complaints;
complying with laws;
any other purpose you agree to;
our legal obligations, assisting government and enforcement bodies or regulators, or where otherwise required or authorised by law, or an order of a court or tribunal.
4. Who will we disclose your personal information to?
We may disclose personal information about you:
to our related companies and to Nissan Foundation Australia Ltd;
to our agents or contractors. These include businesses we use such as mailing houses, insurers, printers, information technology service providers, lawyers, accountants, debt collection agencies, and other service providers;
to our dealers, but only if they use it for the same purposes as set out above and only in connection with the Nissan dealership franchise;
anyone else that you agree may get the information from us;
any disclosure which is required or authorised by law.
Your personal information may be given to our parent company in Japan, our related companies and our service providers that are located or hold data elsewhere in the world, including New Zealand, United Kingdom, Thailand and United States of America. If it is disclosed to an overseas recipient, we will only do this where we have taken reasonable steps to ensure that overseas recipient will engage with the personal information in a way that is consistent with the Australian Privacy Principles and our instructions or where we reasonably believe they are subject to laws that protect your personal information in the same or substantially the same way as the Australian Privacy Principles.
We will take reasonable steps to protect and keep secure the personal information we hold.
If personal information held by us is lost or there is unauthorised access or disclosure, we will investigate. We will also notify the breach to the Information Commissioner and affected individuals if we are required to do this under the Privacy Act.
5. How do we use your personal information for marketing?
We may contact you with marketing material about our other products or services, special offers, promotions and events that may be of interest to you. We can do this if you have agreed, or when you would reasonably expect that your information would be used or disclosed this way.
We may also share your personal information with our related companies, Nissan Foundation Australia Ltd, and our dealer network, so they can provide you directly with marketing material about their products and services.
6. How can you stop marketing communications?
At any time, you may opt out of receiving marketing communications by contacting us at:
Nissan Motor Co. (Australia) Pty Ltd
Phone: 1800 035 035
Email: csc@nissan.com.au
7. How can you access your personal information?
You may ask for access to personal information we hold about you by contacting the Privacy Officer at the address below. Where we hold information that you can access, we will try to give you choices about how you can access (e.g., emailing or mailing it to you). We may charge a fee to cover the cost of getting your information.
If you think personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, you can ask us to amend it. We will amend the information if we agree with you, or make a record of your comment.
8. Do you have a question or complaint?
If you have any questions about this policy or you have a privacy issue or complaint, please contact us:
The Privacy Officer
Nissan Motor Co. (Australia) Pty Ltd
Locked Bag 2004
BRANDON PARK VIC 3150
Phone: 1800 035 035
Fax: (03) 9797 4400
Email: csc@nissan.com.au
We will respond and tell you we agree with your complaint. If we do not agree, we will give reasons. If we do agree, we will tell you what action we will take.
If you are still not happy, you can contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:
Phone: 1300 363 992 (local call cost, but calls from mobile and pay phones may incur higher charges). If calling from overseas (including Norfolk Island): +61 2 9284 9749
TTY: 1800 620 241 (this number is dedicated to the hearing impaired only, no voice calls.)
TIS: Translating and Interpreting Service: 131 450 (If you don’t speak English or English is your second language and you need assistance and ask for the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner).
Post: GPO Box 2999 Canberra ACT 2601
Fax: +61 2 9284 9666
Email: enquiries@oaic.gov.au
You can also make a complaint to the Australian Financial Complaints Authority at https://www.afca.org.au/about-afca/contact-us/ or by calling 1800 931 678.
9. Privacy and our website
You can visit our website without telling us who you are. The information that you give us on our website will depend on the services you use. In some parts of our website you might have to give us personal information like your name and email address. We will only ask for personal information if we need it to provide a service to you or to comply with the law.
We us cookies to collect information about your browsing history (including on external websites). This information does not identify you personally. We collect this information to improve your online experience. The cookies customise the advertising you see.
The internet is not completely secure. We can’t guarantee the security of personal information you provide online. We will not be liable for breaches of security or unintended loss or disclosure of that information. This does not exclude our liability in any way that is not allowed by law.
Nissan Financial Services Australia Privacy Policy
This is the Privacy Policy of Nissan Financial Services Australia Pty Ltd ABN 70 130 046 794. We may change this policy by publishing an updated version on this website.
1. What personal information about you do we collect and hold?
We may collect and hold personal information about you. This includes:
your name, address, email, telephone number, date of birth and other information about you such as age and gender;
credit related information when you apply for credit from us or we get a credit report about you;
details about your vehicle purchase and servicing such as purchase date, purchase details, vehicle registration, name of selling dealer, service history and repair, warranty and recall details;
information you give us, such as when you contact our Customer Service Centre, login to our website, or call our roadside assistance;
from marketing campaigns, product surveys, and research, when you access and use our social media platforms and any publicly available information;
any other personal information we have to collect to identify you;
details in identity documents given to us, such as passport number, driver’s licence number, Medicare card number; and
payment details including bank account, credit card details and other payment information if you buy our products and services.
We will only collect sensitive information about you if you agree, unless the law lets us, or when the law says that we must collect it. Sensitive information includes information about your religious beliefs, ethnic origin, race and health.
If you give us personal information about another person, please tell them you have given it and tell them about this policy.
We keep records of privacy consents that we get from you.
We hold your personal information in secure electronic and physical files.
2. How do we collect and hold your personal information?
Usually we collect personal information about you from you and from Nissan dealers who received information from you.
We may collect personal information about you:
when you contact us by email, phone, in person, by SMS or other forms of communication, including our website or our social media platforms;
when you take part in promotions, competitions, customer surveys, and sponsorships;
when you fill in order forms for a vehicle, parts or accessories, or book your vehicle for servicing;
when you apply for credit;
when you contact us about any of our products and services; or
from related companies, dealers and our service providers (such as Roadside Assist).
We may also collect personal information about you from other people such as:
your accountant or employer, when required, as part of your credit assessment;
any personal referee provided by you;
any credit provider that gave credit to you, to assess your credit application;
any credit reporting body that gives us a credit report about you;
your insurer or broker;
our agents;
any government authorities;
marketing agencies and marketing lists; and
other people you refer to us or who refer us to you.
3. What do we do with your personal information?
We collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for:
meeting our obligations to you (including warranty, recall, and roadside assistance) as the owner or driver of a vehicle;
answering your inquiries or comments;
customer service and product development;
to assess your application for credit;
to assess your application for a product or service;
deciding whether to offer you additional credit or to renew credit;
developing, administering and managing our services and businesses;
promotions and marketing including direct marketing;
research to improve our websites, products or services;
any other customer support purposes;
dealing with complaints;
complying with laws. These laws include:
the Anti-Money Laundering and Counter-Terrorism Financing Act 2006, which requires us to collect personal information about you when verifying your identity;
the National Consumer Credit Protection Act 2009, which requires us to make inquiries about you when assessing an application for credit by you; and
the Personal Property Securities Act 2009, under which we may need to collect personal information about you to record a security interest on the Personal Property Securities Register;
any other purpose you agree to;
our legal obligations, assisting government and enforcement bodies or regulators, or where otherwise required or authorised by law, or an order of a court or tribunal.
4. Who will we disclose your personal information to?
We may disclose personal information about you:
to our related companies and to Nissan Foundation Australia Ltd;
to our agents or contractors. These include businesses we use such as mailing houses, insurers, printers, information technology service providers, lawyers, accountants, debt collection agencies, and other service providers;
to our dealers, but only if they use it for the same purposes as set out above and only in connection with the Nissan dealership franchise;
anyone else that you agree may get the information from us;
any disclosure which is required or authorised by law, including to AUSTRAC in respect of any suspicious or threshold transactions or activities; and
if you have applied for credit from us:
to a credit reporting body, to get a credit report about you and/or to allow the credit reporting body to maintain a credit information file containing information about you;
to a debt collection agency;
to identity verification vendors including credit reporting bodies who use your government identifiers (for example your driver’s licence number or passport number) to verify your identity for us;
your employer or former employer (for example, to conduct a reference check for finance applications);
with your consent, to other credit providers for the purpose of assessing your application for credit; or
with your consent, to guarantors or proposed guarantors if a credit arrangement is or will be guaranteed.
Your personal information may be given to our parent company in Japan, our related companies and our service providers that are located or hold data elsewhere in the world, including New Zealand, United Kingdom, Thailand and United States of America. If it is disclosed to an overseas recipient, we will only do this if we have taken reasonable steps to ensure that overseas recipient will engage with the personal information in a way that is consistent with the Australian Privacy Principles and our instructions or where we reasonably believe they are subject to laws that protect your personal information in the same or substantially the same way as the Australian Privacy Principles.
We will take reasonable steps to protect and keep secure the personal information we hold.
If personal information held by us is lost or there is unauthorised access or disclosure, we will investigate. We will also notify the breach to the Information Commissioner and affected individuals if we are required to do this under the Privacy Act.
5. How do we use your personal information for marketing?
We may contact you with marketing material about our other products or services, special offers, promotions and events that may be of interest to you. We can do this if you have agreed, or when you would reasonably expect that your information would be used or disclosed this way.
We may also share your personal information with our related companies, Nissan Foundation Australia Ltd, and our dealer network, so they can provide you directly with marketing material about their products and services.
6. How can you stop marketing communications?
At any time, you may opt out of receiving marketing communications by contacting us at:
Nissan Financial Services Australia Pty Ltd
Phone: 1800 035 035
Email: nfsa_csc@nissan.com.au
7. How can you access your personal information?
You may ask for access to personal information we hold about you by contacting the Privacy Officer at the address below. Where we hold information that you can access, we will try to give you choices about how you can access (e.g., emailing or mailing it to you). We may charge a fee to cover the cost of getting your information.
If you think personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, you can ask us to amend it. We will amend the information if we agree with you, or make a record of your comment.
8. Do you have a question or complaint?
If you have any questions about this policy or you have a privacy issue or complaint, please contact us:
The Privacy Officer
Nissan Financial Services Australia Pty Ltd
Locked Bag 2004
BRANDON PARK VIC 3150
Phone: 1800 035 035
Email: nfsa_csc@nissan.com.au
We will respond and tell you we agree with your complaint. If we do not agree, we will give reasons. If we do agree, we will tell you what action we will take.
If you are still not happy, you can contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:
Phone: 1300 363 992 (local call cost, but calls from mobile and pay phones may incur higher charges). If calling from overseas (including Norfolk Island): +61 2 9284 9749
TTY: 1800 620 241 (this number is dedicated to the hearing impaired only, no voice calls.)
TIS: Translating and Interpreting Service: 131 450 (If you don’t speak English or English is your second language and you need assistance and ask for the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner).
Post: GPO Box 2999 Canberra ACT 2601
Fax: +61 2 9284 9666
Email: enquiries@oaic.gov.au
You can also make a complaint to the Australian Financial Complaints Authority at https://www.afca.org.au/about-afca/contact-us/ or by calling 1800 931 678.
9. Privacy and our website
You can visit our website without telling us who you are. The information that you give us on our website will depend on the services you use. In some parts of our website you might have to give us personal information like your name and email address. We will only ask for personal information if we need it to provide a service to you or to comply with the law.
We us cookies to collect information about your browsing history (including on external websites). This information does not identify you personally. We collect this information to improve your online experience. The cookies customise the advertising you see.
The internet is not completely secure. We can’t guarantee the security of personal information you provide online. We will not be liable for breaches of security or unintended loss or disclosure of that information. This does not exclude our liability in any way that is not allowed by law.
10. How do we manage your credit-related information?
We have a credit reporting policy about how we manage credit-related personal information including the kinds of information we collect, how we collect and hold that information, what we use that information for, and who we may disclose the information to. Our credit reporting policy is available at Nissan Financial Services Australia Credit Reporting Policy.
Nissan Financial Services Australia Credit Reporting Policy
This is the Credit Reporting Policy of Nissan Financial Services Australia Pty Ltd ABN 70 130 046 794. We may change this policy by publishing an updated version on this website. We also have a privacy policy which is available at Nissan Financial Services Australia Privacy Policy.
1. What credit information about you do we collect and hold?
The kinds of credit information that we may collect and hold about you includes information (other than sensitive information) that may be provided to us from a credit reporting body, including:
identification information such as name, any alias or previous name, date of birth, gender, current or last known address and 2 previous addresses, and driver licence number;
information about consumer credit provided to you including the name of the credit provider, whether the credit provider is an Australian credit licensee, the type of consumer credit, the day on which the consumer credit is entered into, the terms or conditions of the consumer credit that relate to repayment, the maximum amount of credit available under the consumer credit, and the day in which the consumer credit ends;
information about whether or not you met an obligation to make a monthly payment of consumer credit, the day on which the payment is due, and the day on which the payment is made;
a statement that an information request has been made to a credit reporting body in relation to you by us;
the type of consumer credit or commercial credit, and the amount of credit, sought in an application made by you to a credit provider, when a credit provider has made an information request;
information about payments that are at least 60 days overdue for consumer credit and more than $150;
information that an overdue payment has been paid;
information about arrangements with credit providers;
information about court judgments (but not for criminal proceedings) against you that relate to credit applied for or given to an individual;
personal insolvency information;
publicly available information that relates to your activities and credit worthiness and that is not court proceedings information about you or information about you that is entered or recorded on the National Personal Insolvency Index; and
the opinion of a credit provider that you have committed a serious credit infringement in relation to consumer credit.
If we get credit reporting information on you from a credit reporting body, or we get information from it that has any bearing on your credit worthiness and could be used in deciding your eligibility for consumer credit, we refer to this information as “credit eligibility information”. The types of credit eligibility information that we hold includes the credit information listed above. It may also include information such as credit scores and assessments which we generate from this information.
2. How we collect and hold credit information and credit eligibility information about you?
We collect information from you by telephone, in person or in documentation such as an application for credit. We may also collect information when you make a request or enquiry of us.
We may also collect information about you from other people such as:
your accountant or employer, as part of your credit assessment;
your personal referee;
a credit provider that gave credit to you, to assess your credit application;
a credit reporting body that gives us a credit report about you;
an insurer.
We will hold credit information and credit eligibility information in secure electronic and physical files.
We will take reasonable steps to protect and keep secure the credit-related information we hold.
If credit-related information held by us is lost or there is unauthorised access or disclosure, we will investigate. We will also notify the breach to the Information Commissioner and affected individuals if we are required to do this under the Privacy Act.
3. Why do we collect hold, use and disclose credit information and credit eligibility information about you?
We may collect, use, hold and disclose credit information and credit eligibility information when permitted by law:
to assess an application for credit or a guarantor;
to use a credit reporting body;
to manage credit that we provide;
to assist customers avoid defaulting;
to collect debts;
to comply with laws;
to deal with complaints;
to assist other credit providers to do these things; and
for other lawful purposes.
4. Disclosing credit information to a credit reporting body
We may disclose credit information about you to a credit reporting body. The credit reporting bodies that we are likely to disclose your credit information to are:
Equifax – www.mycreditfile.com.au – 1300 762 207
Experian – www.experian.com.au – 03 8622 1600
Illion – www.illion.com.au – 13 23 33
If we disclose your credit information to a credit reporting body:
the credit reporting body may include the information in reports provided to credit providers to assist them to assess your credit worthiness; and
if you do not meet your payment obligations in relation to consumer credit or commit a serious credit infringement, we may disclose this to the credit reporting body.
Each credit reporting body has a policy about the management of credit-related personal information. You can get a copy by contacting the credit reporting body using its contact details above.
5. What are your rights under the Privacy Act?
Your rights under the Privacy Act in relation to credit-related information include:
You can get the credit reporting body's policy about the management of credit-related personal information by contacting it. See contact details above.
You can access credit-related information that we hold about you from us, if you want to request us to correct the information, or make a complaint.
You can request a credit reporting body not to use credit reporting information about you for pre-screening of direct marketing by a credit provider.
You can request the credit reporting body not to use or disclose credit reporting information about you if you believe on reasonable grounds that you have been or are likely to be a victim of fraud.
6. Do we send your credit-related information overseas?
Your credit information or credit eligibility information may be given to our parent company in Japan. If it is disclosed to an overseas recipient, we will only do this if we have taken reasonable steps to ensure that overseas recipient will engage with the credit information in a way that is consistent with the Australian Privacy Principles or reasonably believe they are subject to laws that protect your personal information in the same or substantially the same way as the Australian Privacy Principles.
We will also take adequate measures to ensure that the information is handled by the overseas recipient in accordance with the Privacy Act and our instructions.
7. How can you access credit eligibility information?
You may ask for access to credit eligibility information we hold about you by contacting the Privacy Officer at the address below. Where we hold information that you can access, we will try to give you choices about how you can access (e.g., emailing or mailing it to you). We may charge a fee to cover the cost of getting your information.
If you think credit eligibility information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, you can ask us to amend it. We will amend the information if we agree with you, or make a record of your comment.
8. Do you have a question or a complaint?
You can make a complaint about a breach of Part IIIA of the Privacy Act (which deals with credit reporting) or the Privacy (Credit Reporting) Code. Please contact us at:
The Privacy Officer
Nissan Financial Services Australia Pty Ltd
Locked Bag 2004
BRANDON PARK VIC 3150
Phone: 1800 035 035
Email: nfsa_csc@nissan.com.au
We will respond and tell you we agree with your complaint. If we do not agree, we will give reasons. If we do agree, we will tell you what action we will take.
If you are still not happy, you can contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:
Phone: 1300 363 992 (local call cost, but calls from mobile and pay phones may incur higher charges). If calling from overseas (including Norfolk Island): +61 2 9284 9749
TTY: 1800 620 241 (this number is dedicated to the hearing impaired only, no voice calls.)
TIS: Translating and Interpreting Service: 131 450 (If you don’t speak English or English is your second language and you need assistance and ask for the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner).
Post: GPO Box 2999 Canberra ACT 2601
Fax: +61 2 9284 9666
Email: enquiries@oaic.gov.au
If your complaint relates to your finance with us, you can also make a complaint to the Australian Financial Complaints Authority at https://www.afca.org.au/about-afca/contact-us/ or by calling 1800 931 678.
9. How can you get copies of this policy?
You can ask us to provide you with a copy of this policy, including a hard copy, by contacting us using the contact details above.
Privacy
